Regardless of which type of networking event you attend, the number one thing
无论你参加什么样的社交活动 能帮你在这些活动中把握机会
that will help you navigate all of them is having a great elevator pitch.
的第一法宝就是一场精彩的电梯演讲
Elevator pitches were originally known as sales pitches and
电梯演讲最初称为推销话术
lived solely in the business world.
仅存在于商界
However, they soon became popular across all industries because it was a way for
但是 它很快在各行各业流传开来 因为这是一种使人们
people to quickly communicate the purpose and value of something.
快速传达目的和价值观的方式
Having a elevator pitch is invaluable in your career development.
电梯演讲对于职业发展非常重要
These short sentences will find their way in your LinkedIn summaries,
这些简短的句子可以作为你领英资料中的自我总结
in talking to a recruiter, in small talk with friends, or
与招聘人员交谈的核心内容 或与朋友聊天的重点
in requesting a promotion.
或要求升职时的说辞
Elevator pitches also help outside of networking, such as in a job interview,
电梯演讲在社交之外也很有用 比如在一场面试中
when the employer asks you why you're applying or what you're interested in.
当雇主问你为什么应聘这个岗位 或你对这个岗位感兴趣的方面是什么时
I have to admit that I did not like my first experience with elevator pitches.
我必须承认我的第一次电梯演讲经历并不是很好
I was at a professional development event and was put in with a group
当时我在参加一个职业发展活动 周围全是一群
of strangers, and we all had to respond to the prompt, tell me about yourself.
陌生人 而每个人都必须回答一个问题“请介绍一下你自己”
I was first.
我是第一个
I rambled.
我漫无边际地说了一通
I've locked a lot of that experience from my memory, but
我将那次经历的很多记忆都封锁起来了
I'm sure I sounded like this, hi, I'm Trinh.
但我记得我当时是这样说的 大家好 我是 Trinh
I grew up in the San Francisco Bay Area, and I go to school.
我在旧金山湾区长大 我上过学
And I'm interested in education, but I've never worked in education.
我对教育行业感兴趣 但是我从来没从事过教育工作
And yeah, that's why I'm here today, to help me make that transition.
是的 这就是我今天为什么来这里 就是希望能帮我做出这个转型
I was really embarrassed.
我尴尬极了
Especially when everyone else gave their answers and
特别是当别人给出他们的答案时
it sounded like they had their life together.
他们听起来有条有理
But it was also a great learning experience because after hearing myself,
但这对于我来说也是一次重要的学习经历 因为在反思了自己所说的话时
I kept thinking, why do I need to tell people where I grew up?
我不断想  我为什么要告诉别人我是在哪长大的？
Is that really important for my career?
这对于我的职业来说重要吗？
Why did they need to know that I was transitioning careers or
他们为什么需要知道我正在转换职业
that I was new to this industry?
或者我新入这个行业？
I was at the event, doesn't that mean I was already interested?
我参加了这个活动 不就意味着我对此感兴趣吗？
This experience taught me that if I wanted to sound confident and
这次经历教会我如果我想听起来自信并且
communicate well, I needed a concise elevator pitch that showed what I wanted
能清楚地表达我的想法 我需要一个简洁的电梯演讲 说明我想要什么
and why I wanted it.
以及原因
My elevator pitch now is,
现在我的电梯演讲是这样的
I'm a project manager passionate about personalized education.
我是一名项目经理 对个性化教育具有很大的热情
After working in non-profits and public policy,
在从事过非营利和公共政策领域的工作后
I believe lifelong learning is the solution to many societal issues.
我相信终身学习是解决很多社会问题的答案
I'm excited to apply my teaching and management skills at Udacity.
我很高兴能在优达学城运用我的教学和管理技能
So, let's dive in to how to develop an elevator pitch with personal branding in
好的 下面我们就来看看如何准备电梯演讲 并在其中结合
mind.
个人营销